https://www.palacecasinoresort.com/privacy-policy/

HomeHotelCasinoPromotionsDiningSpaGolfNewsBlogDirections / MapEmail List
Revised: 3/15/2016
We hope that you enjoy our luxurious facilities, our exciting entertainment, and our quality customer service. Because we value your patronage and respect your privacy, we are providing you with this PALACE CASINO RESORT Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy pertains to the PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites and the PALACE CASINO RESORT defined below (collectively, “us” or “we”). This Privacy Policy describes how Personal Information (defined below) about you may be used and disclosed by PALACE CASINO RESORT in the course of business. It also describes how you can opt-out of some uses of Personal Information. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. You may contact us at info@palacecasinoresort.com.
I. SCOPE OF PRIVACY POLICY
A. PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites
This Privacy Policy is applicable only to the website that posts this Privacy Policy (“PALACE CASINO RESORT Website”). It does not apply to any other web sites, including other web sites that may be owned, operated, or affiliated with PALACE CASINO RESORT or its affiliates. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of each PALACE CASINO RESORT web site you visit to learn about that particular web site’s privacy practices.
II. VISITORS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES
The PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites are maintained on servers located in the United States, and Personal Information is also stored on computers located in the United States. The United States may not offer a level of privacy protection for Personal Information, which includes Confidential Personal Information (defined below), as great as that offered in other jurisdictions. Therefore, the disclosure of Personal Information pursuant to this Privacy Policy is at your own risk. We make no representation that the practices described in this Privacy Policy are compliant with laws outside of the United States that apply to the collection, security, use and disclosure of Personal Information. PALACE CASINO RESORT will use its best reasonable efforts to maintain the security of Personal Information.
III. TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT
A. Personal Information
“Personal Information” is information through which you can be identified. We collect Personal Information that you provide voluntarily at PALACE CASINO RESORT Website and PALACE CASINO RESORT. We also collect Personal Information that you provide voluntarily by e-mail, postal mail, telephone, and other means. Personal Information that we may collect through PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites includes your name, date of birth, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, gender, credit card information, gaming activity, and your purchase and reservation information. In addition to the
Personal Information listed above, Personal Information that we may collect at PALACE CASINO RESORT includes driver’s license number and state, social security number, passport information and naturalization information. When you complete a marker play application at any PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Site or PALACE CASINO RESORT we may also collect the name of your firm, your firm’s address and telephone number, your position with the firm, and banking information (including the name and address of your primary and secondary banks along with your account numbers). Some Personal Information
described above is considered “Confidential Personal Information.” Confidential Personal Information includes your name associated with one or more of the following: date of birth, credit card information, driver’s license number, state ID card, social security number, passport information and naturalization information. Personal Information may also include your image in a live video feed that can be viewed on the PALACE CASINO RESORT Website if you visit PALACE CASINO RESORT. We may combine Personal Information with other generally or publicly available information to help us identify your preferences or interests. Your Personal Information may also be merged with Personal Information available from other sources, including (1) e-mail address or postal address append services; (2) credit card verification and credit services; and/or (3) other resorts, casinos, or properties that are owned, operated, or affiliated with PALACE CASINO RESORT or its affiliates.
B. Non-Personal Information
“Non-Personal Information” is information about you or your activities through which you cannot be personally identified. When you use the Internet, your web browser or client software may transmit certain information to the servers that host the web sites you visit. The information may include the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, your geographic location, and your movement within and interaction with the PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites, including what pages you look at and what information you download. When you visit PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites, our servers collect such Non-Personal Information. We use this Non-Personal Information for a variety of purposes including to generate aggregate statistics about visitors to PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites. In situations where it is possible to do so, Non-Personal Information may be linked to Personal Information.
C. Information Collected Utilizing Cookie Technology
PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites utilize a website technology known as “cookies.” A cookie is a small file that contains information sent by a web site that is saved on your hard drive by your computer’s browser. Cookies store information that a web site may need to personalize your experience and to gather web site statistical data, such as which web pages you visit, what material you download, your Internet provider’s domain name and country, and the addresses of web sites you visited immediately before and after visiting a particular web site. PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites use cookies to collect
and store your preferences for viewing the PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites, such as whether you disable a particular function, so that you will not have to disable the same function on following visits. The cookie information may also be used to detect and resolve web site problems and to assist with customer support concerns. In addition, PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites utilize cookies to provide a unique identifier to your computer. This helps us to generate statistics regarding usage of PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites, such as the percentage of repeat visitors. In situations where PALACE CASINO RESORT has Personal Information, the unique identifiers may be matched with Personal Information. In addition, when you book a reservation online to stay at PALACE CASINO RESORT, the reservation or confirmation number may be stored in a cookie on our computer and in an order file generated by third party vendors that assist in processing and fulfillment of PALACE CASINO RESORT reservations. To browse the Internet and PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites without using cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when each cookie is offered so that you can accept or reject each cookie.
However, if you reject all cookies, you may not be able to conduct some transactions or use some services on PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites. D. Information Collected From Partners We may obtain Personal Information from carefully selected business partners and other entities that direct you to, or are located at, PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites and/or PALACE CASINO RESORT (collectively, “Partners”). We may use Personal Information obtained from our Partners in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. We generally have no control over how our Partners use Personal Information they
collect from or about you. Therefore, if you provide Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, to our Partners, we encourage you to consult our Partners’ privacy policies for more information about their privacy protection practices.
E. Information Collected by Other Third Parties
Certain transactions and services offered while visiting PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites may be processed or provided by third parties under contract with us for fulfillment and other purposes. When your Personal Information is submitted to these third parties for such purposes, we require those third parties to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided.
IV. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
A. Uses by PALACE CASINO RESORT
1. Use for Marketing Purposes
We may use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for our own marketing purposes, including notifying you of special promotions, offers and events via postal mail, e-mail, telephone, text messaging, and other means. We will not permit Confidential Personal Information to be used for marketing purposes. If you do not want us to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such uses by notifying us (see Section V below).
2. Use for Non-Marketing Purposes
We may use Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, and Non-Personal Information for purposes unrelated to marketing, including: (1) responding to your inquiries, complaints and other communications; (2) processing and fulfilling reservations and/or purchases and making a record of such reservations and purchases; (3) contacting you for confirmation or customer service after reservations and purchases are made or after you sign up for or participate in certain activities; (4) for statistical or demographic analysis; (5) for tracking reservations and corresponding hotel stays generated
through our affiliate program and calculating and/or auditing commissions that may be paid in relation to a hotel stay; (6) to help improve PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites and services; and (7) to customize your experience at PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites. Opting-out of the use of your Personal Information for marketing purposes will not prevent your Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, from being used for non-marketing purposes.
B. Sharing within PALACE CASINO RESORT and with Affiliates
Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information may be shared for any purpose among PALACE CASINO RESORT and PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites. Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information may also be shared for any purpose with PALACE CASINO RESORT affiliates not covered by this Privacy Policy, and any other resorts, casinos, or other properties that are owned, operated by or affiliated with PALACE CASINO RESORT or its affiliates (collectively, “Affiliates”). Your Confidential Personal Information will only be shared to the extent necessary to permit PALACE CASINO RESORT to validate your identity for the purposes of extending credit, completing a purchase transaction, recording of gaming related activity or other legitimate non-marketing business needs. If you do not want your Personal Information to be shared among PALACE CASINO RESORT, PALACE CASINO RESORT
Web Sites and Affiliates for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by notifying us (see Section V below).
C. Sharing With Partners for Marketing Purposes
We may share your Personal Information and Non-Personal with our Partners for joint marketing efforts, or for our Partners’ own marketing purposes. Your Confidential Personal Information will not be shared with Partners for marketing purposes. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with Partners for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by notifying us (see Section V below). When we provide Personal Information to our Partners, we require those Partners to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided. To determine how Partners use the Personal Information they collect directly from you, or about you, from sources other than PALACE CASINO RESORT, please consult the privacy policies of our Partners.
D. Sharing With Partners and Other Third Parties for Non-Marketing Purposes
Although you may request to opt-out of sharing Personal Information for marketing purposes, we reserve the right to disclose Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, to our Partners and other third parties for the following purposes: (1) for non-marketing purposes, including reservation or purchase fulfillment; (2) in the event of a transfer to a third party of all or substantially all of the assets of PALACE CASINO RESORT, and/or any PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Site; (3) to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other valid legal process; (4) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; (5) to protect and defend PALACE CASINO RESORT, its affiliates and affiliates, and all of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys and agents in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; (6) to satisfy any contractual obligation to indemnify its contractors, Partners or other third parties in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; (7) to enforce the Terms of Use of PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites; (8) to prevent imminent physical harm or threats to public safety; (9) to third party vendors that PALACE CASINO RESORT may use to perform functions on behalf of PALACE CASINO RESORT, such as companies that process credit card transactions; (10) to prevent fraud; and (11) to engage in debt collection. When we provide Personal Information to our Partners and other third parties for such purposes, we require those Partners and third parties to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided.
V. How to Opt-Out
If you wish to opt-out of receiving solicitations from us, or do not want us to share your Personal Information with Partners, for marketing purposes, you can email us at info@palacecasinoresort.com, call 1-800-PALACE-9, or write to:
PALACE CASINO RESORT
Attn: Marketing
P.O. Box 309
Biloxi, MS 39533-0309
If you do not want us to share your Personal Information among PALACE CASINO RESORT and PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Sites or Affiliates for marketing purposes, you may email us at info@palacecasinoresort.com, or call 1-800-PALACE-9.
VI. SECURITY
Non-Personal Information and Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, collected by the PALACE CASINO RESORT Website and PALACE CASINO RESORT is stored on secure servers. The secure servers are protected by firewalls and a multitude of other industry standard security measures. These security measures are instituted to ensure the protection of these secure servers from unauthorized access. However, no security system is impenetrable, and these systems could become accessible in the event of a security breach. We have controls in place that are designed to detect potential data
breaches, contain and minimize the loss of data, and conduct forensic investigations of a breach. Our staff is required to take reasonable measures to ensure that unauthorized persons cannot view or access your Personal Information. Employees who violate our privacy policies are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. We cannot enforce or control the security of the computers, electronic devices, or electronic communication method that a consumer may utilize to send e-mails and submit information to us over the Internet. You are responsible for ensuring that the computers, electronic devices and electronic communication methods you utilize will provide adequate security for communicating with us. We are not responsible for the disclosure or interception of your information before we receive it. As a standard security practice, we will take reasonable steps, which are standard in the industry to ensure that the communication methods used to support the PALACE CASINO RESORT Website do not permit connection or communication by methods that have known security weaknesses or vulnerabilities. As such, if you experience trouble using an PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Site, it may be an
indication that you need to upgrade your Internet browsing tool or application to a newer version that supports more secure communication methods.
VII. CONNECTIONS (LINKS) TO THIRD PARTY WEB SITES
When you connect (link) to unaffiliated third-party sites, including sites operated by our Partners, through the PALACE CASINO RESORT Website, we are not responsible for, and cannot control the information collection or privacy practices of those sites. It is important that you review and understand the privacy policies posted on any linked sites you visit, before providing any Personal Information. These sites may also collect cookies, or allow third-party advertisers on their sites to collect cookies. You can often find information regarding a site and its privacy policy (if one exists) on the site’s home page. If you cannot find a site’s privacy policy or do not like a site’s privacy policy, you may prefer not to conduct business with, nor provide information through, that site.
VIII. PERSONS UNDER AGES 18 AND 21
Certain areas and activities at PALACE CASINO RESORT and PALACE CASINO RESORT Website are intended for use only by persons 21 years of age or older. If you are under the age of 21, we ask that you do not access or attempt to access any portions of the Web Sites that are restricted to persons age 21 or older, including but not limited to any Web Sites containing password-restricted information (see PALACE CASINO RESORT Terms of Use for more information). We reserve the right to verify your age at any time for any reason and may refuse admittance or service to a person who does not have valid age identification
at any time. PALACE CASINO RESORT abides by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect or allow the collection of Personal Information from persons under the age of 21. If the parent or guardian of a person under 21 believes that the person has provided us with Personal Information, the parent or guardian of that person should contact us at info@palacecasinoresort.com and request that such Personal Information be deleted from our files. If a person under the age of 21 submits Personal Information, we delete the information as soon as we discover the source of the
submission, and we do not use the information for any purpose.
IX. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. When this Privacy Policy is revised the revised Privacy Policy will be available at the PALACE CASINO RESORT and will be posted on the PALACE CASINO RESORT Website. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Personal Information or Non Personal Information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy. You should periodically review the Privacy Policy available at PALACE CASINO RESORT and the PALACE CASINO RESORT Website for revisions. You are encouraged to bookmark the Website to check for updates and take or print out copies of the Privacy Policy for your records. Use of an PALACE CASINO RESORT Web Site after revision of the Privacy Policy signifies your consent to the revised Privacy Policy. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@palacecasinoresort.com.
Top
